wonderlic.com 2019-07-09

# Privacy - Wonderlic

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applies to Wonderlic, Inc.’s (“Wonderlic”) website and all its online application platforms (“Website”) and describes Wonderlic’s practices for handling personal information provided to Wonderlic over the Internet. By visiting the Website ([www.wonderlic.com](https://www.wonderlic.com/)) you are accepting the practices described in this Policy.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

Wonderlic collects personally identifiable information (“PII”) that you provide in optional, voluntary submissions, such as forms, user profiles, free signups, contest entries, requests for customer service, software and mobile applications downloads, and via certain third party sources. If Wonderlic directly combines information from third parties with data it has collected from you, Wonderlic will treat the combined information as PII and handle it in accordance with this Policy. See Third Party Analytic Services Section herein below.  
The types of personal information Wonderlic may directly collect about you through the Website includes the following–only if you decide to provide such information: (a) contact information (e.g., name, address, e-mail address, phone/fax numbers, employer name, job title) in connection with your expression of interest in receiving information about Wonderlic and its products; (b) your resume information and employment application information in response to Wonderlic’s job openings or its clients job openings; and (c) any other PII that you may voluntarily provide to us in an online form or through an e-mail. If you are using this Website to create an account with Wonderlic, we collect the information requested on our account application form, including contact information and financial information (such as credit card number or billing information). This information is used for internal purposes, such as account establishment, billing, fulfillment of orders and customer service.

When you apply for employment with a prospective employer (Wonderlic client) or seek promotion with a current employer (Wonderlic client) through the Website, PII about you will be collected for use in connection with the application or promotional process. This information may include but will not necessarily be limited to your name, email address, address, social security number, prior work history and other background information. This information will be used by the specific employer for assessing your suitability for employment or promotion with that employer, record keeping, governmental reporting and compliance with legal obligations or as reasonably necessary to defend the rights of the specific employer or Wonderlic. In the course of the application process, this information may also be disclosed to others such as companies hired by the specific employer to perform background checks, to government agencies and to third-party vendors who assist the specific employer in performing its business functions. Information collected through the Website may also be disclosed in the following situations: (a) in response to a subpoena, court order or legal process, to the extent required by law; (b) to protect user security or the security of other persons, consistent with applicable laws; or (c) in connection with a sale or transfer of relevant Wonderlic assets.

**COOKIES**

A Cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from Wonderlic’s website to the hard drive of your computer. This unique number identifies your computer, web browser and Internet specifications, but not you personally. Specifically, it does not provide PII about you, such as your name and address. Wonderlic uses Cookies to measure traffic patterns, personalize content and control security. Wonderlic tracks the usage of the Website in order to modify it according to our customer’s needs. Wonderlic monitors and pays attention to what information is requested and attempts to make it easier to locate in the future. Please note, Wonderlic does reserve the right to link IP addresses and information supplied by the ISP to PII to facilitate efforts to protect the integrity and security of Wonderlic’s systems. Enabling Cookies on your browser is not required to use our Website, but will assist you with using its various functions and tools, such as recognizing your name or password when you return to the site.

**THIRD PARTY ANALYTIC SERVICES**

Wonderlic may use third party services, such as Google Analytics, to collect anonymous visitor data from the Website. Wonderlic may use these services to collect anonymous visitor information like IP addresses, browser types (e.g., Internet Explorer, Safari, Chrome, Firefox, Mozilla), the accessing app, or referring pages and websites. Wonderlic may use these third party services to collect such non-PII for various purposes, such as: (i) providing anonymous statistical analysis of web page traffic patterns; (ii) administration of our services and servers; (iii) allowing for auditing of our services by third parties and (iv) improving our general services. Additionally, Wonderlic may use other third party analytic services that independently collect PII from other sites and online mobile products and services related to your activities across their network of websites and online mobile products and services.

**HOW WONDERLIC USES YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

Wonderlic does not share your PII with any third party without your authorization. Notwithstanding, Wonderlic may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide information on individual users to the relevant governmental authorities. Also, in matters involving a danger to personal or public safety, Wonderlic may voluntarily provide information to appropriate governmental authorities. By using Wonderlic’s website or its online platforms you consent to the international transmission of information provided to us. Internet transmissions/emails sent to us may not be secure. As a result, these are sent at your own risk.

**WHAT SECURITY PROCEDURES ARE IN PLACE TO PROTECT MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?**

Wonderlic’s website and platforms have security measures, such as firewalls and other security technologies, in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we take reasonable precautions to prevent such occurrences. Any other particularly sensitive information, such as your credit card number, collected for a business transaction is encrypted prior to transmission to your credit card company.

**INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN**

Wonderlic does not offer services to children under the age of 13, and this web site is not directed at children under the age of 13. Wonderlic does not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13.

**LINKS**

Wonderlic’s website may use content or provide links to third party websites. Wonderlic has no control over third parties and assumes no responsibility in connection with your use of third party content or websites. We recommend that you check the terms of use and privacy policy of any website before providing any personally identifiable information.

**UPDATING AND CORRECTING INFORMATION**

You may correct your personal information by contacting us by email (Attn: Customer Services), by mail at Wonderlic Customer Services, 544 Lakeview Parkway, Suite 210, Vernon Hills, IL 60061 or by phone at +1 877.605.9496.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

Wonderlic may revise this policy from time to time. If there is a material change to this Policy, we will post the revised policy at this location. We recommend that you periodically review this Policy to be informed of how Wonderlic is protecting your information.

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, you may contact us at:  
David Arnold  
Wonderlic, Inc.  
544 Lakeview Parkway  
Suite 210  
Vernon Hills, IL 60061  
+1 847.247.2602
